The Godfather ditched his own
victory banquet
with his new bride.
The whole continent’s
wondering where the Godfather
took his wife for their honeymoon.
But there’s no
way they’d hide out
in a shithole
border town like this.
Old man, where's this month's protection money?
Please, sir!
You've already collected three times this month!
We have nothing left!
No money?
Your girl's pretty.
Her virginity will do.
Take her!
No!
- Father, help me!
- Please, spare my daughter!
Let her go.
Who the hell are you, kid?
Mind your own business.
You know who backs me?
The Holy Knight
of the Sovereign Sanctum!
Holy Knight? What's that?
I could make him kneel
with a flick of my finger.
What bullshit!
Make a Holy Knight kneel?
You think you're the Godfather?!
Only he can do that!
That's right.
I'm the Godfather.